CURRICULUM VITAE

Md Pintu Info

https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-pintu-b12486147/

Contact No: +91: 8851443850 / 8826416027

Email Id: mdpintudl@gmail.com

Address: J-4/72, Khirki Extension Malviyanagar,

New Delhi-110017.

OBJECTIVE:

Looking forward for the right opportunity and willing to work under a reputed and large-scale organization which provides exposure to new ideas and where my best technical, analytical capability and 4 years + of experience in Redcube Digital Media Pvt. Ltd. can also be utilized for organizational as well as personal growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

2018-2019 UI DEVELOPER

Brinztorm Technical Excellence Pvt. Ltd

I have worked at this Company since April 25, 2018 to Sep 20, 2019 as a UI Developer.

2019-Present SR. UI DEVELOPER

Redcube Digital Media Pvt. Ltd

I am working at this Company Since Dec 17, 2019 as a UI Developer

WEBSITE

https://www.thequizopedia.com/

https://www.protinex.com/ https://www.danone.in/

https://danonenutriciaacademy.in/

https://www.yakult.co.in/ https://gutfoundation.org.in/

https://www.fmri.in/

https://www.gatewayofhealing.com/

https://dramitgisurgeon.com/ https://shivohamfoundation.co.in/

http://love-you-slin.in/

https://www.amrihospitals.in/

QUALIFICATION

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

Web Designing and Development from Arena Animation, Delhi in 2017.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

- B.Sc. (IT) from ISBM University (2017-20)
- 10+2 (K.B Jha College Katihar) from BSEB (2013-15)

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES

- Create the Website or landing page on HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, REACT JS, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP5, SHOPIFY, WORDPRESS coding for promotion and newsletter mailers.
- Create the web shop creative on Adobe Photoshop for all website banner and email html template
- convert Html to React js
- Html to Wordpress

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- HTML5/ CSS3
- JavaScript
- React js
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Wordpress
- Shopify
- Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES:

Participated in Cricket Match Tournament in 2013 in block level

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Nationality : Indian

Languages : English and Hindi

Strength : Ability to teach myself to meet the requirements of the others and for me

: Good team member with ability to work under pressure.

: Good management skills.

Place: New Delhi (Md Pintu)